<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9">
  <url>
    <loc
      >https://tmrev.io/movie/256112-101 Ways (The Things a Girl Will Do to Keep
      Her Volvo)</loc
    >
    <lastmod>2022-11-27</lastmod>
  </url>
  xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9"
  xmlns="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1"
  xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc
      >https://tmrev.io/movie/256112-101 Ways (The Things a Girl Will Do to Keep
      Her Volvo)</loc
    >
    <lastmod>2022-11-27</lastmod>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc
        >https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w500/qQA95FP6TGHDaLvXbYUQi8dUMRH.jpg</image:loc
      >
      <image:caption
        >101 Ways (the things a girl will do to keep her Volvo) chronicles the
        epic adventures of Watson (Wendy Hoopes), a struggling young writer who
        moves to the quiet suburbs to write her first novel. A New York City
        native, Watson isn't much of a driver, and her over-protective mother
        forces her to buy a car she can't afford - a brand new Volvo. Watson
        falls in love with the car, but real life quickly catches up to her in
        the form of the repo man when she falls behind on her monthly payments.
        To avoid losing her beloved wheels, Watson tries her hand at two of the
        oldest professions: waiting tables and phone sex. At the same time, her
        meddling best friend (Jamie Harrold), convinces Watson to ignite her
        stagnant love life by pursuing a sexually-phobic pilot (Gabriel Macht)
        and an aloof supermarket cashier (Glenn Fitzgerald). The result is a
        refreshing comedy packed with star cast performances and an overriding
        moral: life's long and winding road has as many speed bumps as
        straightaways.</image:caption
      >
      <image:title
        >101 Ways (The Things a Girl Will Do to Keep Her Volvo)</image:title
      >
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
