<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9">
  <url>
    <loc
      >https://tmrev.io/movie/547007-Alter Bridge: Live at the Royal Albert Hall
      (featuring The Parallax Orchestra)</loc
    >
    <lastmod>2022-11-27</lastmod>
  </url>
  xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9"
  xmlns="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1"
  xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc
      >https://tmrev.io/movie/547007-Alter Bridge: Live at the Royal Albert Hall
      (featuring The Parallax Orchestra)</loc
    >
    <lastmod>2022-11-27</lastmod>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc
        >https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w500/gP0DvYxpVwHnyEYvtuV62hrbQc0.jpg</image:loc
      >
      <image:caption
        >Some nights are just pure magic! In October of 2017, hard rock titans
        Alter Bridge took to the stage of the iconic Royal Albert Hall in London
        for two very special headline shows. Myles Kennedy, Mark Tremonti, Brian
        Marshall and Scott Phillips treated the capacity crowds to selections
        from their entire musical catalog. The set list included some of the
        band’s biggest hits; rarities and even a few songs the band had never
        previously performed live. Adding another career first for the band,
        Alter Bridge was joined on stage by conductor Simon Dobson and the
        52-piece Parallax Orchestra. Together, everyone on stage during those
        two extraordinary nights treated the combined crowd of over 10,000 fans
        to an unforgettable music experience. Now those two performances have
        been combined in to one full length, epic concert that is to be shared
        with fans around the globe in Alter Bridge: Live At The Royal Albert
        Hall.</image:caption
      >
      <image:title
        >Alter Bridge: Live at the Royal Albert Hall (featuring The Parallax
        Orchestra)</image:title
      >
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
