<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9">
  <url>
    <loc
      >https://tmrev.io/movie/61707-Bazaar Bizarre: The Strange Case of Serial
      Killer Bob Berdella</loc
    >
    <lastmod>2022-11-27</lastmod>
  </url>
  xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9"
  xmlns="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1"
  xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc
      >https://tmrev.io/movie/61707-Bazaar Bizarre: The Strange Case of Serial
      Killer Bob Berdella</loc
    >
    <lastmod>2022-11-27</lastmod>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc
        >https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w500/xbc3tW0S4NrPi8kbSHAjMHVmITK.jpg</image:loc
      >
      <image:caption
        >In 1988, Chris Bryson was found running down a Kansas City street
        naked, beaten, and bloody wearing nothing but a dog collar and a leash.
        He told police about Bob Berdella, a local business man and how Berdella
        had caputed him, held him hostage, raped him, tortured him and
        photographed him over several days. Police later arrested Berdella and
        searched his home where they found several hundred polaroid photographs,
        a detailed torture log, envelopes of human teeth and a human skull. It
        was soon discovered that Berdella had murdered 6 young men in his home
        after drugging them and performing his sick acts of sexual torture. Some
        lived the horrors for only a few days, one for 6 weeks. After death
        Berdella would cut up the bodies with an electric chain saw and a bone
        knife, place the body parts in empty dog food bags for trash collection
        on Monday. Although he denied this, it is believed that Berdella used
        organs of the victims as in food dishes he would serve at his
        shop.</image:caption
      >
      <image:title
        >Bazaar Bizarre: The Strange Case of Serial Killer Bob
        Berdella</image:title
      >
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
