<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9">
  <url>
    <loc
      >https://tmrev.io/movie/64927-Darwin's Struggle: The Evolution of the
      Origin of Species</loc
    >
    <lastmod>2022-11-27</lastmod>
  </url>
  xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9"
  xmlns="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1"
  xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc
      >https://tmrev.io/movie/64927-Darwin's Struggle: The Evolution of the
      Origin of Species</loc
    >
    <lastmod>2022-11-27</lastmod>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc
        >https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w500/yk9Z5mS2hpYZMHFyjA1KO4HKlmC.jpg</image:loc
      >
      <image:caption
        >Documentary telling the little-known story of how Darwin came to write
        his great masterpiece, On the Origin of Species, a book which explains
        the wonderful variety of the natural world as emerging out of death and
        the struggle of life. In the twenty years he took to develop a brilliant
        idea into a revolutionary book, Darwin went through a personal struggle
        every bit as turbulent as that of the natural world he observed.
        Fortunately, he left us an extraordinary record of his brilliant
        insights, observations of nature, and touching expressions of love and
        affection for those around him. He also wrote frank accounts of family
        tragedies, physical illnesses and moments of self-doubt, as he laboured
        towards publication of the book that would change the way we see the
        world. The story is told with the benefit of Darwin's secret notes and
        correspondence, enhanced by natural history filming, powerful imagery
        from the time and contributions from leading contemporary biographers
        and scientists.</image:caption
      >
      <image:title
        >Darwin's Struggle: The Evolution of the Origin of Species</image:title
      >
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
